

# RAJESWARY DEAVI GUNASEGARAN

#### CONTACT

- 01127630826
- rajeswarydeavi.95@gmail.com
- Saujana Rawang, 48000 Rawang, Selangor

#### **LANGUAGE**

- English
- Malay
- Tamil

#### **SKILLS**

- Time Management
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership
- Problem-solving
- Effective Communication
- Flexibility

#### **EXPERTISE**

- MS Office
- Basic Math
- Spreadsheets
- Customer Service
- Quality Assurance
- Data Entry
- Laptop & PC System
- Communication tools

## **PROFILE**

Versatile professionaln with years of experience in warehouse administration, office assistance, and quality analysis and more. Known for strong organizational skills, attention to detail, and process improvement. Adaptable and quick to learn, consistently enhancing efficiency and delivering excellent results. Passionate about contributing to team success and continuous improvement.

## **EDUCATION**

#### SMK(P) TAMAN PETALING, JALAN GASING

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia 2011 - 2012

#### SMK(P) TAMAN PETALING, JALAN GASING

Penilaian Menengah Rendah 2008 - 2010

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Shopee My, Eco City KL

Content Moderator (Video)

- Review user generated content (UGC).
- Enforce community guidelines.
- Handle reports of inappropriate content.
- Monitor user behavior and trends.

# Floor Place Sdn.Bhd, Sungai Buloh

Administration cums Customer Service

- Handles enquiries, new order (PO), delivery orders (DO), emails, calls, whatsapp and walk in customers.
- Handles all the clerical works on a daily basis.
- Handles daily filing scanning n e-filing.

#### **Shopee Sg, Sunway Visio**

Customer Services Representatives cum Technical support

- Answer incoming calls and handle customer complaints.
- Handling with Sellers and Buyers regards on the shipment.
- Handling and arranging pick up with Logistics.

2024 - Present

2023 - 2024

2020 - 2021

#### REFERENCE

Available on request.

# **EXPERIENCE**

## **IKGL International Logistics Sdn Bhd, PJ**

2019 - 2020

# Warehouse Administrator cums HR Administrator

- Answer incoming calls and handle DHL WhatsApp customer complaint.
- Make a report for the monthly returned item.
- Dealing with staff payroll and OT, other benefits calculation.

#### SINGTEL (SUDONG), Klang

2018 - 2019

# Inbound Telemarketer cum Technical support (Telesales) & Trainee Team Leader

- Representative duties includes taking phone calls, assisting
- customers, solving customer complaints, placing orders,
- Scheduling appointments, and following up on outbound calls.
- · Assisting team with the sales issue.

# SAMSUNG (SME), TMone Damansara Kim

2017 - 2018

#### **Quality Assurance / Analyst**

- Maintain and develop internal support and call center quality standards.
- Following up with outbound calls based on case and project.
- Review a subset of support agents' conversations (calls, emails, chat etc)

#### **SUNWAY MEDICAL CENTRE, Sunway**

2016 - 2016

#### **Business Office Assistant**

- Handled customer registration profile.
- Handled customer complaints and suggestions.
- Handles customer insurance registration.

# ASTRO (M), PJ

2015 - 2016

# Outbound telemarketer (Telesales)

- Handled all the outbound calls. (auto-dialed)
- Handles overdue/debt customers.
- Handle cases/complaints and escalate based on the cases.